Guide to the Marilyn Yalom Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Marilyn Yalom papers
1977-1987
SC1227
Yalom, Marilyn
1.5 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Access Terms
Stanford University. Center for Research on Women.; Stanford University. Michelle R. Clayman Institute for Gender Research.; Women --History --Study and teaching (Higher) --United States.; Women --Social networks.
Collection Contents
- Center for Research on Women (CROW), 1977-1987; Accession ARCH-2015-030
  - Yalom, Marilyn - Memos To/From, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Yalom - Correspondance, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Letters to and from Yalom, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Documents - The Female Experience: Victorian Heritage, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Lit 263: Victorian Heritage, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Victorian Heritage Part II, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Sense of Identity in Modern Women Writers, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Gender and Genre, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - MTL 208: Autobiography & Lit. -- Gender & Genre, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Coming to Light - Correspondance, Permissions, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Maternity, Mortality & Lit of Madness (reviews), 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Conferences and Lecture Series, 1980-1987 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Women's Autobiogs. in French, 1973-1939 (Bibliography) (Correspondence), 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Women's Autobiographies, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Women's Autobiographies in England France & Germany, 1973-1939 (Schenk Project: Bernard Coll.), 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Jewish Studies, American Jewish Women Writers, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Yalom, Marilyn - Memos To/From, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Yalom, Marilyn - Memos To/From, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 18)